and moving on we've got prudential
assurance malaysia berhad from malaysia
with their programme
financial protection and financial
education
[Applause]
[Music]
on behalf of prudential assurance
malaysia berhad it is an honor for me to
accept this award from asia responsible
enterprise award 2021
in the social empowerment category
in prudential our purpose is to help
people get the most out of life
and this includes the community in which
we operate
we aim to build financial resilience
among underserved families and children
in malaysia
therefore our work with pukase
our flagship program where we provide
financial protection
and financial education to urban
low-income families and children
it is our way to provide financial
freedom and peace of mind to these
communities
in malaysia kashi means love
and that is what pukase is all about
giving love to the underserved
communities especially during these
trying times
thank you to the organizers enterprise
asia for this award